厄尔  我说了让你拖门口的地
Earl, I told you to mop the entrance.
这地板比喜剧中心台的
That floor is dirtier than Bob Saget
艺人吐槽大会还"脏"
at a Comedy Central roast.
你知道你听起来需要什么东西吗  暴躁妹
You know what it sounds like you need, cranky lady?
经痛药加巧克力棒
A Midol and a Dove bar.
你也招子放亮点  奥列格
You watch it, too, Oleg.
就像厄尔的髋骨  你也能被换掉
Like Earl's hip, you can be replaced.
你有发现自从麦克斯与卡洛琳走了
Have you noticed since Max and Caroline have been away,
阿憨这个小婊子脾气变很大吗
Han is getting a little big for his bitches?
我叫他小婊子了吗
Did I say bitches?
我故意的
'Cause I meant to.
我才不要被一个小我40岁的人颐指气使
I will not be bossed around by someone 40 years younger than me.
他又不是我第二任老婆
He is not my second wife.
我要打给餐厅的保安
I am calling diner security.
啥事上门找我啊  厄尔
What's up, Earl?
除了你的血压往"上"之外
I mean, besides your blood pressure.
你们什么时候回来
When are you coming back?
我们明晚回来
We're coming back tomorrow night.
卡洛琳马上要签电影的合同了
Caroline's about to sign the movie contract,
所以我不用省钱  陆运邮寄自己回去了
which means I don't have to come home UPS Ground.
你在跟餐厅的人讲电话吗
Are you on the phone with the diner?
我感觉都能闻到餐厅的味儿了
I feel like I can smell it.
我觉得我们几个撑不过明天了
I don't think any of us are gonna make it past tomorrow.
阿憨最近牛逼得像这里是他地盘一样
Han's been walking around like he owns the place.
这里本来就是我的地盘
I do own the place!
优步司机很不喜欢被人挠痒痒啊
Boy, Uber drivers do not like to be tickled.
说到意想不到的事
And speaking of things no one would see coming,
我跟兰迪用了F开头的字了
I used the F-word with Randy.
谁会意想不到这事啊
Who wouldn't see that coming?
你整天都在用这个字[fuck]
You use the F-word all the time...
通常还是在孩子与神职人员面前
usually around children or clergy.
不是脏话 是"未来"[future]
No, the F-word as in "Future."
麦克斯  你为未来做计划了吗
Max, you made plans for the future?
你连跟我计划一下晚餐都不愿意
You won't even make dinner plans with me.
你总是说"我们到时是不是朋友都不一定"
You always say, "Who knows if we'll still be friends by then?"
你总是提前了  大概有5小时问我
Well, you always ask me, like, five hours ahead of time.
麦克斯  我要用那个C打头的字了
Max, I'm gonna go ahead and use the C-word.
我要称你们俩为"情侣"了
I'm calling you and Randy a couple.
我要说件事
I'm gonna say something,
但我不想要你兴奋过头
and I don't want it to go to your head.
你说得没错  小贱人
You're right, bitch.
你看  麦克斯  一切都圆满
See, Max, it all worked out,
到此时此刻  然后接下来就有坏消息了
right up until what I'm about to say right now.
我们明天得坐接驳巴士去机场
We have to take the shuttle to the airport tomorrow,
因为我们还得穷27个工作日
'cause we're still poor for another 27 business days.
我们退场要有范儿  租个派对巴士吧
Let's go out in style and get a party bus.
过了这么多年  你跟我之间
After all these years, we still have
对于"范儿"的定义还是天差地远
such different concepts of style.
来嘛
Come on!
车上有钢管
With a stripper pole
还有一锅鸡鸡型香肠
and a Crock-Pot of cocktail weenies.
我在派对巴士上面当过一年舞女
I danced on a party bus for a year,
不是为了赚钱哦
not for money.
我们才不坐派对巴士
We are not taking a party bus.
这不是你的什么欢庆16岁派对
This isn't your super sweet 16.
我没有欢度过16岁
I didn't have a sweet 16.
我当时在水管工学校上学
I was in plumbing school.
大家安安
Hey, everybody.
我不知道是怎么了
I don't know what's going on,
但电梯里的人都用奇怪眼神看我
but people on the elevator were looking at me funny.
苏菲
Sophie!
怎么
What?
我牙齿上卡有菜叶吗
Do I have spinach in my teeth?
没卡菜  只有大概25根针卡在你脸上
Uh, no spinach, but about 25 needles stuck in your face.
它们是来帮助我怀孕的
Yeah, they're helping me get pregnant.
我那位治疗师让我去找阿毛
My healer Audra sent me to Mao,
受明星喜爱的针灸师
the acupuncturist to the stars.
没错  他比多情男星"捅"过的明星还多
Yep, he's poked more famous people than John Mayer.
苏菲  你不应该针还没拿掉就离开诊所啊
Sophie, you're not supposed to leave with those needles,
就像我们不应该带走这些小瓶子一样
just like we're not supposed to leave with these vases.
这样吧  我要做一件我以前
Tell you what, I'm gonna do what I used to do
为我在酒馆里的美女阿姨做过的事
for my Aunt Becky at the Elks Lodge.
我要为你弄走脸上的针[面前的白痴]
I'm gonna get some pricks out of your face.
麦克斯  你觉得兰迪邀我一起来吃饭
Max, do you think Randy invited me to dinner
是来见证他问你是否愿意异地恋吗
to witness him asking you to be bicoastal?
我这个睫毛膏好像不防水
'Cause I don't think this mascara's waterproof,
而我看到那场面绝对会感动哭
and I'm definitely gonna cry
喜极而泣  外加几滴嫉妒的眼泪
happy and a few jealous tears.
我从来没有过双岸恋[东西岸]
I'm never been bicoastal.
我曾双性恋过一周
I was bisexual for a week,
但那基本上是因为我要搭便车
but that's mostly because I was hitchhiking.
你们到啦
There they are.
这是我们第一次见面的那桌
Oh, this is the table where we first met,
你以为我是个廉价妓女
and you thought I was a cheap hooker.
而当时你只猜对了一半
And you were only half right.
我要落泪了  比想象中更嫉妒一点
Here they come, more jealous than I expected.
来庆祝吧
Let's celebrate.
今晚是你们俩的大日子
It's a big night for both of you.
卡洛琳  你的电影成功签约
Caroline, your movie deal closed,
而麦克斯  我找到了你的袜子
and Max, I found your sock.
在我冰箱底发现的
It was under my refrigerator.
这就说得通了
Oh, that makes sense.
我当时想要用叉子跟我袜子做的鱼竿
I was trying to fish an M&M out from under there
钓出一颗掉到底下的巧克力豆
with a fishing hook I made with a fork and my sock.
当时钓出来后我太兴奋
I was so excited about getting the M&M
就忘了那袜子了
that I abandoned the sock.
麦克斯  你知道你以后再也不需要
Max, you know you don't have to eat candy
吃掉到地上的糖了
that fell on the floor anymore.
我还是会  但知道我有选择的余地感觉很棒
I still will, but it's nice to know I don't have to.
天啊  你飞上枝头变凤凰了
Oh, my God, your whole life is changing.
我们再等个人就行了
We're just waiting for someone else.
不是吧  你帮我邀请了男伴吗
Oh, no, did you invite a guy for me?
应该早点让我知道
I wish I'd known,
因为我只刮了裙子以下的腿毛
'cause I only shaved up to the bottom of my dress.
不是给你找的男伴
It's not a date for you.
是为我跟麦克斯来的
It's someone here for me and Max.
我通常都是等在一起一个月
Wow, I don't usually bring up threesomes
房事开始无聊了才会提议3P
till the one-month mark when things start to go stale.
跟我脑海中幻想的完全不一样
Oh, definitely wasn't picturing this guy.
你好  我叫艾略特·查尔斯
Hello, I'm Elliot Charles.
两个名字  稍微有趣点了
Okay, two first names, slightly more interesting.
来算个杂交数学  这里有四个人
So doing the orgy math here, there's four of us,
在这之中  麦克斯和我裸体时不能碰对方
and out of the four, Max and I can't touch naked.
她定的规矩  不是我
Her rule, not mine.
我来这里跟性事并无关系
Oh, I'm not here in a sexual capacity.
我是兰迪的心理医生
I'm Randy's therapist.
我想我们该开始正事了
And I guess we should get started.
我9点在别处还有活儿
I do have a 9:00 in the valley.
有个13岁的姑娘要跟她吃全素的父母
A 13-year-old girl is coming out to her vegan parents
出柜坦白"对肉有兴趣"
as meat-curious.
这是怎么回事
Um, what's happening?
是这样的  麦克斯  艾略特
Look, Max... Elliot?
是这样的  麦克斯
Look, Max,
我的病人  兰迪
my patient, Randy,
要跟你分手
is breaking up with you.
什么
What?
麦克斯  我知道这很突然
Max, I know this sounds abrupt.
艾略特
Elliot?
麦克斯  我在行医生涯中发明了
Max, in my practice, I developed
快速撕下创口贴大法
the ripping-the-Band-Aid-off technique.
有一天你可以在我的书里读到
You'll read about it in my book someday,
前提是我写完
if I ever finish it,
但这就是我跟我心理医生之间的事了
but that's between me and my therapist.
他现在不愿意跟我说话
He's not speaking to me right now
因为我把他沙发弄脏了
because of a couch spill.
如果不是老子也是心理医生
And I'd be mad as hell about it
早就因为他不理我火冒三丈了
if I didn't completely understand it!
再问一句  这到底是演哪出
And now, again, what's happening?
看起来你好像是在通过心理医生
Because it seems like you're breaking up with me
来跟我分手啊
using a therapist.
看起来的确是这样
It does seem that way.
艾略特
Elliot?
他的确是通过心理医生在跟你分手
He is breaking up with you using a therapist.
听好了  兰迪
Look, Randy?
卡洛琳
Caroline.
听好了  艾略特  你请兰迪像个爷们点
Look, Elliot, you tell Randy to be a grown-up
用短信跟麦克斯分手好吗
and break up with her over text.
至少发一个"再见  友尽"的表情图吧
At least send her a "Bye, Felicia" Bitmoji.
-我们走  -麦克斯  别这么走掉
- Let's go. - Max, don't go like this.
艾略特  别让麦克斯这么走掉
Elliot, don't let Max go like this.
麦克斯  你伤心了
Max, you're hurt.
你觉得被抛弃了
You're feeling abandoned.
现在什么最能帮到你呢
What would be really helpful to you right now
是我的书  如果我能写下一章
is my book, if I can just get one chapter on paper.
人们都将受用无穷啊
I think people would benefit a lot from the book.
我们要走了
Well, we're leaving.
真是难以置信
This is shocking,
这年头姐已经很难被吓到了
and it's really hard to shock me
尤其是上次看到一只老鼠
since that time I saw a mouse
在我沙发上干操一个土豆之后
dry-humping a potato on my couch.
听好了
You know what?
你留着我的袜子[打飞机]吧
You can keep my sock.
但转念一想  还给我把
On second thought, I need it.
麦克斯  等等
Max, wait.
我要直接走了  因为上次我这么生气时
I am just gonna go, because the last time I was this mad,
某人失去了一边的眉毛
someone lost an eyebrow.
而那次我花了很久的时间
And it took me a long time
才重新长回来呢
to grow it back.
谢谢
Thank you.
麦克斯  快点
Max, hurry!
我们得现在离开  才能带苏菲去见治疗师后
We have to leave now to take Sophie to the healer
还有足够时间去机场
and still be at the airport by noon.
你昏过去的时候我帮你梳过头了
I brushed your hair when you were passed out.
这是我最快的移动速度了
I can't move any faster.
这个手扶梯好像坏了
I think this escalator's broken.
我阻止过你喝第32号瓶
I tried to stop you from drinking bottle number 32,
因为那是辣椒酱
which was sriracha.
但是你完美把我绑在了那张椅子上
But you tied me to that chair so well.
喝下那瓶辣椒酱后
Well, since drinking that hot sauce,
我也算被"绑"在厕所里的某张"椅子"上了
I've been tied to a different chair.
我有东西能让你开心点
I have something to make you feel better.
我不信
I doubt it.
除非是一个装满冰块的尿布
Unless it's a diaper full of ice.
不是这个  我们外面见
It's not that. I'll meet you outside.
好了  好了  还记得那个我不想要
Okay, okay, remember that party bus
而你现在估计也不想要的派对巴士吗
I never wanted and you probably don't want now?
-惊喜  -好时机
- Surprise! - Good timing.
我想自杀  而且还总想要被
I'm feeling suicidal, and I've always wanted
埋在类似这样的地方
to be buried in something like this.
来嘛  麦克斯  开心点
Aw, come on, Max, cheer up.
两根钢管只收一根价钱呢
You're getting two poles for the price of one.
这是人生中首次派对巴士
This is the first time a party bus
不能解决我的所有问题呢
hasn't fixed every problem I have.
那是因为你还没
Well, you haven't seen
看到我的爱国歌曲《星条旗永不落》舞步
my "Stars and Stripes Forever" routine.
波特  这瓶朗姆酒
Um, Bert, is this rum
里面有烟屁股是正常的吗
supposed to have a cigarette butt in it?
如果你想要吐  请吐在地板上
If you gonna puke, please aim for the floor.
我还能用水管冲掉
I can hose it down.
不然我几个月后都能在假皮沙发里找到玉米
Otherwise, I'm finding corn in the pleather for months.
如果我今天呕吐了  肯定不是嗨到吐
Well, if I throw up today, it's not 'cause I'm having fun.
我很开心是因为
I'm just happy because, finally,
车上终于有女人不戴着鸡巴造型帽子了
there's ladies in the bus not wearing penis helmets.
鸡鸡帽都没了
Nope, they were all out of penises,
只好将就戴蛋蛋帽
so I had to settle for balls.
给  姑娘们
Here, girls.
我可以接受白天在派对巴士喝酒
Nope, I will day drink on a bus,
但我接受不了放蛋蛋在我头上
but I will not put balls on my head.
你还奇怪自己为什么会单身呢
And you wonder why you're single.
那家贵得离谱的寿司店
Ugh, there's that crazy expensive sushi place
我和兰迪光顾过
where Randy and I ate.
那家墨西哥卷饼店  我们后来也有去
And there's the taco place we had to eat at afterwards
因为寿司吃不饱
'cause we were still hungry.
麦克斯  拜托  把兰迪抛之脑后吧
Max, please, you have to put Randy behind you.
在那个停车场里  我把兰迪抛之"身后"
And there's the parking spot where I put Randy behind me.
伯特  我们参加的是好莱坞
Bert, did we sign up for the Hollywood
情感终结游吗
relationship death tour?
如果是  我要去参观阿弗莱克和加纳的家
If so, I'd like to hit the Affleck-Garner house.
前面就是他住的地方了
And right up there is where he lives.
在那个肌肉超发达的流浪汉那右转
We'd make a right at that super ripped homeless guy,
往里走两到三个街区  就是兰迪家了
and in two or three blocks, we'd be at Randy's house.
天啊  "我们做这个"  "我们做那个"
Oh, no, "We do this," and "We do that."
她沉浸在"我们"的回忆中
She's "We"-ing.
只要座位没有被尿液"浸"湿
As long as nobody wees on the seats,
我们就万事大吉
we'll be fine.
伯特  在那里拐弯  顺着那条街直走
Bert, turn off there, up that street.
不  等等  你想干什么
No, wait, what are you doing?
想让你得到解脱
You're getting closure.
我要让他亲自面对你  不用那破心理医生代言
I want him to face you without that lame therapist.
就你俩  "面对蛋"交流
Just you and him face-to-testicle.
女士们  咱们要做到哪种程度的跟踪狂
Ladies, just how stalker-y are we getting here?
是去别墅外的路逛一圈
Like a drive around the cul-de-sac?
还是像黛米·摩尔做全套
Or a full-on Demi Moore
还在米娜·古妮丝练瑜伽的地方外面蹲点
outside of Mila Kunis' yoga class?
到了
Ooh, there it is.
前面左边就是了
Up there on the left.
没错  就是那
Yep, there it is.
他也在那  出来遛狗
And there he is letting the dog out.
他全身只围了一块浴巾
Oh, and he's only wearing a towel.
赞啊
Ah, yeah.
现在我懂了  麦克斯
Now I get it, Max.
伯特  走吧  这是个馊主意
Bert, go. This was a bad idea.
不  这是个好主意
No, this is a great idea.
我不会让你把难过的情绪带回纽约
I am not letting you take this bad feeling back to New York.
伯特  开门  我要出去
Bert, open the door. I'm going out.
伯特  关门  开车走人
Bert, close the door. Let's roll.
我本来想穿上衣服
I, uh, wanted to put some clothes on,
但卡洛琳不让
but Caroline wouldn't let me.
这是我认识卡洛琳以来  她做得最明智的事
Oh, that's the smartest thing Caroline's done since I've met her.
麦克斯
Max.
我不在
I'm not here.
麦克斯  你的蛋从枕头后面露出来了
Max, I can see your balls behind that pillow.
我也能看见你的蛋从...
I can see your balls behind that--
苏菲  拜托
Sophie! Come on.
难过着呢
This is sad.
从我坐的地方望去  并不难过啊
Oh, well not from where I'm sitting.
麦克斯  很抱歉我用这种方式处理事情
Max, I'm sorry about the way I handled things.
我只是不知道该如何断绝关系
I just don't know how to break things off.
所以在亚当·桑德勒
It's why I was the lawyer
之前的三部烂片里  我永远都演律师
on the last three Adam Sandler movies.
为什么
Why?
告诉我为什么
I just need to know why.
因为我太年轻  还是太老
Because I'm too young? I'm too old?
难道你有别人  你是别人老公还是老婆吗
Is there someone else? You're married? You're gay?
像这种身材  是基佬一点都不意外
With a body like that, gay is definitely on the table.
你想听真话吗
You want the truth?
我太喜欢你了
I like you too much.
所以我才拖到现在跟你分手
That's why I didn't break it off sooner.
我不舍得结束我们的感情
I didn't want it to end.
这就是你跟我分手的原因吗
That's why you're breaking up with me?
就因为你太喜欢我了吗
Because you like me too much?
至少也是因为在墨西哥有妻儿了吧
At least have another family in Mexico.
麦克斯  我谈过异地恋
Max, I've done the long-distance thing.
或长或短  最后都是以分手告终
It's just putting off the inevitable.
你的生活在那里   我的生活在这里
You have a life there. I have a life here.
这行不通
It doesn't work.
请不要恨我
Please don't hate me.
如果我能  会轻松很多
Be easier if I could.
我要落泪了
Yep, here they come.
打扰了
Pardon me?
今天还要解雇你的管家吗
Are we still firing your housekeeper today?
头饰不错
Oh, nice hat.
印证了一个理论  洛城的女人
Confirms that theory that women in LA
都是有"种"的女人
are the ones with balls.
就是这里了  姑娘们
This is it, girls.
我的治疗师就是在这里施展魔法
This is where my healer does all her magic.
没错  她施法的时候一定出很多汗
Yeah, you know, she must sweat a lot doing it,
因为这房子的味道跟卖相就是那样  对吧
'cause it smells like it looks in here, right?
你说那些罐子里装的都是什么呀
What do you think's in those jars?
瑜伽课上每一个忍住不放的屁吗
Every fart that's ever been held in at yoga?
你还好吗  麦克斯
Are you okay, Max?
大概吧
I guess.
真希望你能提前告诉我  解脱
I just wish you told me closure
就像有人用肌肉车的后尾箱
feels like someone just slammed my nuts
猛夹老娘的蛋一样疼
in the trunk of a Pontiac.
苏菲  我们一个小时内得赶到机场
Sophie, we have to be at the airport in an hour.
我知道  但奥德拉是我怀孕的最后机会
Yes, but Audra is my last chance at getting pregnant.
她准备好了  自然会出现
She'll be ready when she's ready.
不信看看四周
I mean, look around.
种种迹象表明她很专业
She's a professional.
你们有看见一只橙色的猫吗
Have you seen an orange cat?
长了一张不高兴的脸  射手座
A little depressed, Sagittarius?
等等  加菲猫住在这里吗
Wait, Garfield lives here?
奥德拉  她们是麦克斯和卡洛琳
Audra, this is Max and Caroline.
我难得对一个女人这么说
You know, I rarely say this to a lady,
但  搞大奴家肚子吧
but--oh, put a baby in me.
当然好
Absolutely.
你们觉得...你们不...好吧
You think--you don't--okay.
继续说
Go ahead.
抱歉  我在跟我的指导灵们交换意见
I'm sorry, I'm just conferring with my spirit guides.
如果你们同时说话  那我听不清
Well, if you all talk at once, I can't understand you.
懂了
Got it.
他们告诉我  这里的某人
They're telling me that someone here
刚被人伤透了心
just had their heart broken.
是你
It's you.
老天  麦克斯
Oh, my God, Max.
离我近点  坐过来
Come closer to me. Come over here.
真是多谢你
Oh, gosh, thanks a lot.
连我的专用巫女都要抢
You're bogarting my witch.
这些神灵不会骗人
These spirits don't lie.
有时还会过于诚实
A little too honest sometimes.
我又没有问过他们对我刘海的看法
I mean, I didn't ask them if they like my bangs,
可他们却说个不停
but they sure told me.
可多罪受了
It was a whole thing.
你不用帮我
You don't need to help me.
我会忘掉兰迪的
I'll get over the Randy thing.
我遇到过更糟的事情
I've been through worse things,
比如现在这样
like this right now.
不
No.
他们执意要我帮你
They're insisting that I help you.
给我拿个罐子过来
Grab me a jar.
我们将痛苦存放进去
That's where we store the pain...
等了你痊愈之后  我会拿来放扁豆
and lentils, once you're healed.
这下可好
Great.
没男人  可我现在有一个中年女同爱人
No guy, but now I have a middle-aged lesbian lover.
好了  出来了
All right, it's out.
我原以为会需要一个更大的罐子
I thought I was gonna have to move to a bigger jar.
你一定很喜欢这个男人
You must've really liked this guy.
他还不错
He was okay.
他心碎了
Well, he's crushed.
他也真的很喜欢你
He really liked you too.
我以为只有装满花生糖的罐子
Never thought a jar could make me feel better
会让我感觉好些  没想到空罐子也行
that wasn't filled with peanut brittle.
拜托  神灵  搞大奴家肚子吧
Oh, please, spirits, put a baby in me!
好吧  我们开始吧
All right, here we go.
安静  各位
Quiet, everybody.
让我先把门关上
Let me just close the door.
好了
Okay.
等等
Oh, wait.
这里还有别的东西在骚动
There's still some other unrest here.
不行  那个太大了
Oh, no, that's way too big.
是其他东西
It's something else.
真的吗
Oh, really?
你们是说
Oh, you're telling--
当然  当然
Sure, sure.
好的  稍等
Okay. Hold on.
我不能让你怀孕
I can't put a baby in you.
真可惜  苏菲
Sorry, Sophie.
你不能吗
You can't?
你还让我眼睛扎针
You made me put needles in my eyes.
让我跟他们对话
Put me on with them.
我支持你们
Hey, I'm on your side.
她的刘海的确很难看
Her bangs are ridiculous.
厄尔  我们回来了
Hey, Earl, we're back.
姑娘们
Hi, girls.
让我第一个说  欢迎回来
Let me be the first to say welcome back,
还有  最诚挚的慰问
and also, my deepest sympathies.
你还好吗  麦克斯
How are you, Max?
我刚从洛城飞回来
I just flew in from LA,
天啊  我的胳膊累死了
and boy, are my arms tired
因为我要一直揍坐在我旁边那个人
from hitting the person next to me.
那人一直坐立不安  烦死了
They would not stop fidgeting.
我得上厕所  你却不让我出去
I had to pee, and you wouldn't let me out.
麦克斯  卡洛琳  你们回来啦
Max, Caroline, you're back!
我是说  别来无恙
I mean... hello, how are you?
阿憨  你想我们了吧
Han, did you miss us?
拜托  我想你们就像
Oh, please, I miss you like
美国想念某过气电器连锁店
America misses RadioShack.
意外的是  它在我们心中留下了个洞
Surprisingly, it left a hole.
我以前见过你留下一个洞
I saw you leave a hole once...
在土拨鼠日那天
on Groundhog Day.
麦克斯  卡洛琳  苏菲在哪儿
Max, Caroline, where's Sophie?
我好想她
I missed her so much.
知道有句歌词怎么唱吗
You know what they say:
"你不在
absence makes
当我最需要爱  唯有自慰到死"
me have to masturbate almost constantly.
治疗师怎么说
So what did the healer say?
我们让她自己告诉你吧
We'll let her tell you.
大家安安
Hey, everybody!
我从加州回来啦
I'm back from California.
希望我没有
I hope I didn't, like,
被他们的口音带歪  伙计
totally pick up an accent, dude.
我好担心杰瑞米·雷纳
Oh, I was worried Jeremy Renner
会让你成为他此生"进"过的最后一扇"门"
would make you the last thing he'd ever be in.
而我担心的就是你会说这样的话
And I was worried you'd say something exactly like that.
我去我的卡座啦
Well, I'll be in my booth.
治疗师到底怎么说
So what did the healer say?
你多快能怀上孩子
How soon can we get a baby in you?
事实上  奥列格
Oh, well, the truth is, Oleg,
治疗师说她不能
the healer said that she wouldn't be able
帮我怀孕
to help me get pregnant.
苏菲  为什么不能
Oh, Sophie. Why not?
造成我
Well, the reason
不能怀孕的原因是
that I can't get pregnant is...
我已经怀孕啦
I'm already pregnant!
真的
Yeah!
我要当爸爸了
I'm gonna be a father?
对  我已经怀孕三个月了
Yes, I'm three months along.
就是  以后再也不从船上
Yeah, no, that's the last time
买走私货验孕棒了
I'll buy a pregnancy test off a boat.
让我们开了这瓶超便宜的
Well, let's bust out the very cheap,
无酒精香槟吧
non-alcoholic champagne.
无酒精
Non-alcoholic?
对啊  苏菲怀孕了不能喝酒
Yeah, Sophie can't drink when she's pregnant.
好吧
Oh, all right.
那好吧  在飞机上那五杯马天尼酒
Well, then, the five martinis that I had on the plane
是我最后一次碰酒了
were my last.